Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory5 Mss.B.B61.inventory05
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents F
  - Fortune, Reo F. (Box 28)
    - (see Stoyle, R.S., Oct. 11, 1930)
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 15; 3p.
      - from Marg. Mead, 1932 Feb. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 5; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 3; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 13; 1p.
      (Enc: Statement of field expenses of his New Guinea expedition)
    - To Boas, 1934 May 4; 1p.
    - (see Boas, F. to Brander, W.B., May 14, 1934)
    - To Boas, 1934 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 28; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 July 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 10; 2p.
    - (see Boas, F., Sept. 28, 1936)
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 11; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 July 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 28; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 1; 1p.
    - (see Boas, F., Sept. 24, 1940)
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 10; 1p.
      (Enc: Fortune, R.F. The social psychology of Family Life)
      - The social psychology of family life., 1941 Jan. 10; 14.0 p. 14 pages
      - (enc with Fortune, R.F., Jan. 10,1941)
      - Matrilineal and patrilineal cultures in the New Guinea region., 1941 Feb. 8; 5.0 p. 5 pages
      - (see Fortune, R.F. Enc., Feb. 8, 1941.
      - A suggested direction for social science, 1941 Feb. 8; 4.0 p. 4 pages
      - (Enc with Fortune, R.F., Feb. 8, 1941)
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 8; 1p.
      (Enc: His Matrilineal and patrilineal cultures in the New Guinea region.)
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 28; 1p.
      (Enc: Social forms and their biological basis)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 13; 3p.
    - Social form and their biological basis, 1941 Dec.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 1; 3p.
  - Fortune, Mrs. Reo F. -- (see Mead, Margaret)
  - The Forum (Box 28)
    See Leech, Henry Goddard
    See Wildman, Edwin
  - Forum Publishing Co. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p.
  - Fosdick, H.E. (Box 28)
    - From Boas
    - (See Boas, F. to Cadman, S.P., May 29, 1933)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 8
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 1; 1p.
  - Fosdick, R.B. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 1; 1p.
  - Foss, Bertha J. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc: Boas, F. to Lasker, F., Nov. 4, 1939)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 5
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Foss, B.J. to Barlow, S.L.M., Sept. 28, 1939)
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 3; 1p.
      (Enc: Boas, F. to Lasker, F.)
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec.
    - B.J. Foss -- to S.L.M. Barlow, 1939 Sept. 28; 2p.
    - (Enc with Foss, B.J., Sept. 28, 1939)
    - B.J. Foss -- from Novick, Irving, 1939 Nov. 6
    - B.J. Foss -- to Irving Novick, 1939 Nov. 14; 2p.
  - Foster, Allen K. (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 4; 1p.
  - Foster, L[awrence?] (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 20; 1p.
    - Foulché-Delbosc, R. -- to Espinosa, A.M., 1919 Mar. 10; 2p.
  - Fowler, Charles S. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
  - Fowler, Harold (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 19; 1p.
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 27; 1p.
  - Fox, Edward B. (Box 28)
    - To Boas, 1940 May 30; 1p.
  - Fox, Mary (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 11
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 10; 1p.
      (Enc:Reprint from Survey Graphic - Underground Germany)
  - Foy, W[illy?] (Box 28)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 8
    - From Boas, 1908 June 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 May 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 July 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 July 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 July 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 15; 2p.
      (Enc: Liste der für das Rautenstrauch-Joest-museum erwünschten Bücher (Exchange list) - 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 15; 3p.
      (Enc: List of American publications)
  - Frachtenberg, Leo J. (Box 28-29)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 May 10
    - From Boas, 1910 June 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 July 1
    - From Boas, 1910 July 2
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 24
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 1 and 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1913 July 16
    - From Boas, 1913 July 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 19
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1915 May 25
    - From Boas, 1915 May 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 May 26
    - From Boas, 1915 July 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 19
    - From Boas, 1915 Sept. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 29
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept. 29; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1917 May 7
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9
    - From Boas, 1917 June 4
    - From Boas, 1917 June 14
    - From Boas, 1917 Sept. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Sept. 25
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 June 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 June 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 July 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1909 July 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 July 13
    - To Boas, 1909 July 17
    - To Boas, 1909 July 24
    - To Boas, 1909 July 31
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 20; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 6; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 10
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 June 24; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1910 July 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1910 July 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 July 9
    - To Boas, 1910 July 13
    - To Boas, 1910 July 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1910 July 25
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 27; 12p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 19; 9p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 5; 15p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 8; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1911 May 14
    - To Boas, 1911 July 17
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1912 June 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept. 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 13; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 May 12
    - To Boas, 1913 June 30; (telegram)
    - To Boas, 1913 July 3; (telegram)
    - To Boas, 1913 July 26; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 5; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 28; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 13; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 4; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 13; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1915 May 5
    - To Boas, 1915 May 24
    - To Boas, 1915 June 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 July 21
    - To Boas, 1915 July 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 6
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1916 May 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 July 10
    - To Boas, 1916 July 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 27
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 3; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 11; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 8; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 19; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 11; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 5; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 6; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 20; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 May 4
    - To Boas, 1917 May 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 May 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 June 2
    - To Boas, 1917 June 14
    - To Boas, 1917 June 15; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 31; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 6; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 11; 2p.
    - (Enc:Chamberlain, Geo. to Woodrow Wilson), 1917 Dec. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 31; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - (Enc:see B.F. Irvine to George Creel, March 22, 1918), 1918 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 July 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 17; 4p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to H.A. Andrews, 1911 Aug. 17
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to H.A. Andrews, 1912 Feb. 12; 2p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to H.A. Andrews, 1913 June 4
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from H.A. Andrews, 1912 Feb. 8
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from Anon, 1916 May 25
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from H.W. Dorsey, 1917 Nov. 8
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1911 Jan. 4; 5p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1911 Dec. 14; 2p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1912 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1912 Oct. 18
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1913 May 20
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1913 May 20; 4p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1913 June 4; 3p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1913 June 20; 2p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to F.W. Hodge, 1913 July 9; 2p.
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from F.W. Hodge, 1913 May 26
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from F.W. Hodge, 1913 June 11
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from F.W. Hodge, 1917 Nov. 8
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from F.W. Hodge, 1917 Nov. 13
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from C.E. McChesney, 1913 June 6
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from D. Magie, 1917 Nov. 22
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from G.M. Priest, 1917 Nov. 1
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from J.R. Swanton, 1917 Nov. 3
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from C.D. Walcott, 1913 Feb. 13
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from C.D. Walcott, 1917 Oct. 30
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- from C.D. Walcott, 1917 Nov. 7
    - L.J. Frachtenberg -- to C.D. Walcott, 1917 Nov. 2; 4p.
  - Frackenberg, Morris (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 23 and July 2
  - Fracstourgel, R.V. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 30; 2p
  - Fraenkel, Osmund (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - (Enc:Boas, F. to Daily Mirror. Editor, Apr. 19, 1940)
    - (Boas, F. to Winchell, Walter, Apr. 19, 1940)
    - To Boas, 1935 June 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - Fragebogen zur Feststellung der Auswirkungen de Beamntengesetzes vom April 7, 1933 für die Hochschulen., 2p.
      - (enc with Rivet, P., May 13, 1933)
    - "Frances" -- from G.A. Reichard, 1926 July 28
  - Francis (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6
  - Francke, Kuno (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1916 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1917 May 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 29; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 28; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1916 May 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 31; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 May 22; 3p.
  - Franco, E. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 31
    - To Boas
      - (see Efrón, D., Sept. 4, 1937)
    - E.Franco -- from Dalland, J., 1930 July 1
      - (see Uhle, Max. Statement Found at end of June 1933)
    - E. Franco -- Re Museum of Esmeraldas
      - (see Uhle, Max. Statement) Found at end of June 1933
    - E.Franco -- from R.L. Olson
      - (see Uhle, Max. Statement) Found at end of June 1933
  - Franelse, K. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 6
  - Frank, Emil H. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 10; 1p.
  - Frank, Karl George (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Klenze, C.V., 1920 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 June 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 8; 1p.
      (Enc:His letter to Fellinger.)
    - K.G. Frank -- from Emergency society for German and Austrian science and art, 1920 Dec. 31
      - (see Emergency society..art to Speyer, J., Dec. 31, 1920)
    - K.G. Frank -- to Fellinger, 1932 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - (encl with Frank, K.G., Jan. 8, 1932)
    - K.G. Frank -- from Schlesinger, 1920 June 3; 1p.
  - Frank, Lawrence K. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - (Enc: Baumhackl, to Pribham, A.F., July 8, 1926)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 21; 1p.
  - Frank, Marie (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 6
  - Frank, T. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 6; 1p.
  - Frank, Waldo (Box 29)
    - See Boas, F. to Curtis, C., 1933 Feb. 27
    - See Boas, F. to Garner, J.N., 1933 Feb. 27
    - See Boas F. to Walsh, T.J., 1933 Feb. 27
  - Franke, Franz -- to B. Laufer, 1898 Feb. 3 (Box 29)
  - Frank Tourist Co. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 1; 1p.
  - Frankenburger, Charles (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p.
  - Frankfort University Library (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - Frankfurt A.M. Universität. Hohe Medizinische Fakultät. -- from Lampert, H., 1930 Oct. 20
    - (Enc. with Lampert, H., Oct. 22, 1930)
  - Frankfurter, Alfred (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 29; 1p.
  - Frankfurter, Felix (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 July 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 June 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 July 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - F. Frankfurter -- from H. Alexander, 1918 July 6; 2p.
      - (Enc. originally with Grautoff, W., July 7, 1918)
    - F. Frankfurter -- to Pritchett, 1920 June 18; 3p.
    - F. Frankfurter -- to E.R. Seligman, 1926 Mar. 8; 1p.
      - (Enc. with Seligman, E.R., Mar. 31,1926)
  - Frankfurter Verein für orientalische Sprache. der Vorstand (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1913 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 July 5; 1p.
  - Franklin, E.C. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
  - Franklin, H.L. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1934 June 12; 1p.
  - Franklin, W.S. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1928 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 29; 1p.
  - Frantz (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 16; 1p.
  - Franz, L. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 28; 1p.
  - Franz, S.I. (Box 29)
    - To Boas
    - See Keppel, F.P., Nov. 7, 1930
  - Franzen, Raymond (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - R. Franzen -- from K.D. Blackfan, 1930 Mar. 28; 2p.
  - Fraser, T. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 16; 1p.
  - Frassetto, F. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 9
    - F. Frassetto -- from G.G. MacCurdy, 1919 Mar. 8; 1p.
  - Fredericks, Lillian (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 20; 1p.
  - Frederiksen, Svend (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 7; 1p.
  - Free, E.E. (Box 29)
    - See Davies, C.E., Feb. 5, 1931
  - Freeburg, V.O. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 8; 1p.
  - Freeman, Andrew A. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 10; 1p.
  - Freeman, J.E. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 6
  - The Freeman Inc. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p.
      See Huebsch, B.W.
      See Sniton, H.
  - Freiburg Universität (Box 29)
    - Patholog. Institut -- See Aschoff
    - Rektor of Universitat Freiburg in Raden -- from Walz, John S., 1920 Oct. 8; 3p.
    - (Attached to letter of from Walz, John A. to Boas, F.), 10-9-20
  - Freies Deutschland (Wochenzeitung) (Box 29)